paybooks.in 2012-09-15

# 1.

PRIVACY POLICY
Soatech Solution Private Limited ( “Soatech”, “Paybooks”, “"we", "us" and terms of similar
meaning) owns and operates the sites www.paybooks.in, www.ess.paybooks.in and
www.demo.paybooks.in.
By      accessing      the      website     www.paybooks.in       or   www.ess.paybooks.in       or
www.demo.paybooks.in, you are agreeing to accept and comply with the terms and conditions
of use as stated in Terms of Service. The following statement describes the privacy practices
for Soatech. We respect individual privacy and strive to collect and use personal information in
a manner consistent with the applicable laws. Some information provided to us by clients,
customers, contractors and other third parties might be considered private or personal.
Without these details we would not be able to carry on our business and provide our services to
you. We will only collect such personal information if it is necessary for one of our functions or
activities.
ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY
This Online Privacy Policy covers use of the site www.paybooks.in, www.ess.paybooks.in and
www.demo.paybooks.in.
 All information disclosed by visitors is subject to this Privacy Policy. With respect to data
received through its websites, Paybooks will comply with the following:
     1. TYPES AND USES OF INFORMATION
     a. Paybooks gathers personal information from site visitors from time to time in order to
         enhance existing offerings or provide additional services. The company gathers only the
         information essential for understanding visitors in such a way as to provide better
         payroll products and services. This may include contact information such as name, email
         address, telephone number, and company name, and perhaps other data.
     b. Paybooks also may monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help refine and
         improve the design and layout of the website as well as the user experience. As a result,
         Paybooks automatically tracks certain information about site visitors. This information
         includes the users’ browser type, most recent URL and the next URL that the user visits,
         regardless of whether these URLs are on the Paybooks website or not. Paybooks also
         will track visitors’ IP addresses. Paybooks uses this information to, among other things,
         identify broad demographic trends that may be used to provide information tailored to
         users’ interests.
     c. Any personal information given to us through our website is used exclusively by
         Paybooks unless otherwise noted on the site. Paybooks does not make this information
         available to third parties who trade or rent information for direct marketing purposes.
     d. Paybooks does not collect e-mail addresses without the site visitor voluntarily providing
         us with this information (typically via our online information or demo request form,
         whitepaper request form, and other website forms and surveys). Paybooks will

       periodically use that contact information to send visitors e-mail or other
       communications for sales, service, support and marketing purposes. Visitors who do not
       wish to receive marketing e-mail from Paybooks in the future may opt out of receiving
       these communications by following the instructions included in each communication.
    2. LINKS
Our web site may contain links to other web sites and those third party web sites may collect
personal information about you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other
businesses or the content of web sites that are linked to our web site. Paybooks encourages
users to be aware when they leave the site and to read the privacy statements of each and
every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
    3. SECURITY OF INFORMATION
    a) Paybooks endeavours to maintain appropriate safeguards and adequate physical,
       procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage
       facilities so as to prevent any unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or
       modification of personal information. Safeguards include physical protection by the use
       of locked cabinets and technological measures by way of secure access and encryption.
       Paybooks employees are authorized to access personal information based only on their
       need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained.
       Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more
       widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered. We also take
       measures to ensure the integrity of this information is maintained and to prevent its
       being lost or destroyed.
    b) To ensure the integrity and privacy of the personal and credit card information you pass
       to us via the Internet when you make an online transaction, Paybooks has obtained a
       Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Server Certificate, with the strongest level of 128-bit
       encryption. All information collected within a secure page is encrypted while being
       transmitted to Paybooks’ secure server. The server is protected by a firewall that is
       regularly updated when new patches and fixes are released.
    4. NOTIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES/CHOICE
Paybooks reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any
time. All changes will be posted on this page to inform our users what information we collect,
how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. We may e-mail
periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you
should check www.payrollmanagerexpress.com frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated

otherwise, our current privacy notice applies to all information that we have about you and
your account. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less
protective of personal information collected in the past without the consent of affected users.
     5. LEGAL DISCLAIMER
Paybooks may disclose Personal Information when required by law or in the good faith belief
that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, comply with legal
mandates, enforce the terms of use of Paybooks’ website, enforce agreement between
Paybooks and its customers or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Paybooks,
its users and the public.
     6. CONTACTING PAYBOOKS
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings
with this site, please send correspondence to the following address……
